crsdata.com 2017-12-02

# Privacy Policy | CRS Data

## CRS Data Privacy Policy

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.crsdata.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following: 

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. 

  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. 

  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. 

  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. 

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request (e.g. to launch a CRS Data suite or other product you have requested). 

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. 

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address (

[getinfo@crsdata.com](mailto:getinfo@crsdata.com)) or phone number given on our website: 

   • See what data we have about you, if any. 

   • Change/correct any data we have about you. 

   • Have us delete any data we have about you. 

   • Express any concern you have about our use of your data. 

**Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. 

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

**Links**

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. 

**  
Surveys & Contests  
**   
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site and/or our CRS Data products.

**Advertising** As you browse www.crsdata.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with CRS Data. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number. You can visit this page to opt out of [AdRoll’s](https://www.adroll.com/) and their partners’ targeted advertising.

**Updates**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 800.374.7488 or** **via email at getinfo@crsdata.com** **.**

“I say this…and I can’t say it enough-you have a great product, but you’ve got even greater people. And you are extremely responsive. You have a team that can service all 230 banks in my state.”

**COLIN BARRETT** \- Tennessee Bankers Association
